Aida Maisonet

3 Short Street
2nd floor
New Britain, CT 06051
8607705048
Ammaisonet@hotmail.com

OBJECTIVE

To obtain a position in a medical office/facility that will allow me to utilize clinical and administrative skills learned through coursework and training

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Administrative: telephone techniques, computer filing, Knowledge of computer program Microsoft Word, More than seven years experience of outstanding customer service, making audits on registers, and filing employee information such as attendance and quality of work.

Clinical: phlebotomy, obtaining vital signs, performing test, urinalysis, EKG

EDUCATION

Lincoln Technical Institute, New Britain, CT Medical Assistant Program Diploma – May 2011 Studies included: Anatomy & Physiology, Medical Terminology, Medical Laboratory Skills, Pharmacology, Insurance Coding & Billing, Law & Ethics, Business English, Typing & Transcription.CPR certified

EMPLOYMENT

Stop and Shop Newington, CT

March 2008- June 2009

Head cashier, promoted to head cashier after one month, answered phones, resolved customer's problems, resolved any issues cashiers have, prepared schedules, performed audits on registers and cashiers, made bank deposits, provided customer service.

Stop and Shop April 2007- December 2007 Newington, CT Head cashier, answered phones, resolved customer's problems, resolved cashiers' issues, scheduled audits on registers and cashiers, directed the efforts of 6-10 cashiers

Smiles Entertainment Center April 2002- December 2005 Milford, CT Promoted to supervisor within two months; serviced the customer; hosted parties; scheduled and supervised employees; planned and scheduled parties; answered phones and promoted products and services.

Externship

St.Francis Campus Hartford,CT

March 2011 to May 2011

Medical Assistant

As an extern in the Rheumatology office located at St.Francis hospital I scheduled appointments for patients; filled charts; took inbound calls and messages for the physicians; checked patients in and out; faxed patient 's prescriptions to pharmacies; took patient 's vital signs; and documented it in charts; prepared injections and assisted physician with injection